<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SQL to Map Instantly | Visualize BigQuery, Snowflake &amp; Wherobots Data. on</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/</link><description>Recent content in SQL to Map Instantly | Visualize BigQuery, Snowflake &amp; Wherobots Data. on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dekart.xyz/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Blog</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 06:42:12 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Legal</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:20:38 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Documentation</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/docs/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:48:23 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/docs/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Cloud Pricing</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/cloud/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/cloud/</guid><description>Get Your Map in 30 Seconds CloudSelf-Hosted We host it, no technical setup required.
Personal Free Single-person use
Google SSO BigQuery Connector Snowflake Connector Publish Maps Grow $49/month Per editor and admin
Everything from Personal Unlimited Map Viewers Contact Public Map Viewers Manage User Access Max $490/month Unlimited Users
Everything from Personal Unlimited Map Viewers and Editors Contact Public Map Viewers Manage User Access Create Free Workspace
No credit card required</description></item><item><title>Help Dekart</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/support-project/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/support-project/</guid><description>Help Dekart 💜 Dekart is an open-source project. With few amazing contributors, it is still very small. To become sustainable and successful, we need more companies using it, more people active on GitHub, and a larger Slack community.
Choose your involvement
Easy 🌱 Spend 30 seconds
Star Dekart on GitHub&amp;nbsp;🌟
More stars increase the chance for people to discover Dekart and choose to deploy it within their organizations.
Go to GitHub</description></item><item><title>Lightweight CARTO Alternative</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/carto/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/carto/</guid><description>Light alternative to CARTO Dekart is light and fast map analytics for BigQuery and Snowflake. Your data team will create up-to-date maps in seconds with SQL without moving data. Start Free Book a call
Watch short demo video
Why Choose Dekart Over CARTO? Transparent Pricing Free Personal Plan. Grow plans start at $49/month – no surprises, no overpaying. 👉 Dekart Cloud pricing
No Vendor Lock-In Open-source license, commercial code license, SaaS, or self-hosting – Dekart meets any deployment needs.</description></item><item><title>Self-Hosted Pricing</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/self-hosted/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/self-hosted/</guid><description>Your Data. Your Rules. CloudSelf-Hosted You host it. Run Dekart on your own setup. Open-Source Free on GitHub Do it yourself
Run with Docker Connect BigQuery &amp; Snowflake Share maps &amp;nbsp; Premium $5,880/year Enterprise Security
Google SSO Fine-graned access controls Premium codebase Slack support White Label $58,800/year For scalability, and integration
High availability Custom integrations Your branding and SSO 250 hours custom dev included Compare Features Features Open Source View on GitHub Premium Get trial White Label Contact us Core Features Single Docker deployment Create maps with SQL Query BigQuery, Snowflake, Wherobots, or Postgres directly and turn results into live maps.</description></item></channel></rss>