<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Legal on</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/</link><description>Recent content in Legal on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:20:38 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dekart.xyz/legal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>play.dekart.xyz Terms of Use</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/play-terms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:41:21 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/play-terms/</guid><description>TERMS OF USE Last updated February 16, 2021
AGREEMENT TO TERMS
These Terms of Use constitute a legally binding agreement made between you, whether personally or on behalf of an entity (“you”) and dekart.xyz ("Company", “we”, “us”, or “our”), concerning your access to and use of the https://play.dekart.xyz website as well as any other media form, media channel, mobile website or mobile application related, linked, or otherwise connected thereto (collectively, the “Site”).</description></item><item><title>Dekart Cloud Privacy Policy</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/privacy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:17:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/privacy/</guid><description>Dekart Cloud Privacy Policy Effective Date: 2024-03-10
This Privacy Policy outlines how Dekart XYZ UG (haftungsbeschränkt) (“Dekart Cloud,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) manages your data in compliance with the General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) and other relevant laws. By accessing or using our services, you acknowledge that you have read this policy and understand your rights.
Information We Collect and Process Personal Information: We collect your email address solely for authorization, communication, and service delivery purposes.</description></item><item><title>Dekart Legal Notice</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/notice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:17:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/notice/</guid><description>Legal Notice Dekart XYZ UG (haftungsbeschränkt) Rosenthaler Str. 72A 10119 Berlin Germany Tel.: +49 152 3898 2763 Email: nadiia.moiseienko@gmail.com Managing Director: Nadiia Moiseienko Registered at Amtsgericht Charlottenburg Berlin, HRB 260763 B Tax ID: 30 / 257 / 51424 Link to the platform of the European Commission according to Regulation on consumer ODR
Bank account details
Payee: Dekart XYZ IBAN: DE93 1001 0123 5684 0510 42 Bank: 10010123 Account: 5684051042 BIC/SWIFT: QNTODEB2XXX BIC Intermediary Bank (currency other than EUR): TRWIBEB3XXX Impressum Dekart XYZ UG (haftungsbeschränkt) Rosenthaler Str.</description></item><item><title>play.dekart.xyz Privacy Notice</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/play-privacy/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:17:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/play-privacy/</guid><description>PRIVACY NOTICE Last updated February 16, 2021
Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at dekart.xyz (" Company ", "we", "us", "our"). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at bilonenko.v@gmail.com.
When you visit our website https://play.dekart.xyz (the "</description></item><item><title>Terms of Service for Dekart Cloud</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/legal/terms/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Feb 2021 08:17:44 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/legal/terms/</guid><description>Terms of Service for Dekart Cloud SaaS (German version below)
1. Scope and User Eligibility These Terms of Service (Terms) apply to the use of Dekart Cloud SaaS services. Registration requires a valid email address and allows use by an individual or an entity represented by that individual.
2. Service Description Dekart Cloud SaaS provides data visualization for modern data platforms. Users can connect their databases, including BigQuery and Snowflake, query data using SQL, visualize the results, and share them via Dekart Cloud.</description></item></channel></rss>