<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Vladimir Bilonenko on</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/contributors/vladi/</link><description>Recent content in Vladimir Bilonenko on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:50:45 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dekart.xyz/contributors/vladi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why We Stopped using OpenStreetMap and switched to Overture Maps</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/why-we-stopped-using-openstreetmap-and-switched-to-overture-maps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/why-we-stopped-using-openstreetmap-and-switched-to-overture-maps/</guid><description>Switching from OSM to Overture Maps Disclaimer: This article is about OpenStreetMap BigQuery Public Dataset and Overture Maps on BigQuery. Unintentionally this article raised concerns in OSM community. Clarifying edits where added to the article.
Note: Overture Maps dataset is based on OpenStreetMap data plus other sources. It is not a replacement for OpenStreetMap, but rather a more efficient way to access and work with spatial data in the cloud.</description></item><item><title>Compare and optimize BigQuery and Snowflake performance on GIS queries. Part 2.</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/compare-and-optimize-bigquery-and-snowflake-performance-on-gis-queries.-part-2./</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Dec 2024 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/compare-and-optimize-bigquery-and-snowflake-performance-on-gis-queries.-part-2./</guid><description>This second post in the series compares performances of GIS queries between Snowflake. In a previous post, I tested Geometry-in-Polygon Query with constant geometry, showing that without Enterprise-only Snowflake Search Optimization, BigQuery significantly outperforms Snowflake due to spatial clustering.
However, how often do we see constant geometry in real-life pipelines? In my experience, geometry in most cases comes from another dataset.
Get all the roads in Berlin – spatial join. This practical example covers common geometry in polygons scenarios.</description></item><item><title>Compare BigQuery and Snowflake performance on GIS queries.</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/compare-bigquery-and-snowflake-performance-on-gis-queries./</link><pubDate>Tue, 03 Dec 2024 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/compare-bigquery-and-snowflake-performance-on-gis-queries./</guid><description>This is the first in a series of posts comparing BigQuery and Snowflake on GIS query performance. We’ll examine execution times, data scanned, and cost. This test focuses on a Geometry-in-Polygon query using constant geometry—a simple GIS use case.
Setup BigQuery (price $5/Tb data processes) Snowflake (XS warehouse, $2.60/credit) Free Overture Maps Dataset available on both platforms from same provider Dekart to validate visually results Get all the roads in Berlin – constant geometry I started from one most common scenario – geometry in polygons.</description></item><item><title>ST_ Prefix in SQL: A Tale of Time, Space, and Standardization</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/st_-prefix-in-sql-a-tale-of-time-space-and-standardization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/st_-prefix-in-sql-a-tale-of-time-space-and-standardization/</guid><description>As you know, many modern databases and warehouses like BigQuery and Snowflake provide support for map geometry operations. All these functions, like ST_ASGEOJSON are prefixed with ST_. This prefix is reference to SQL/MM Spatial standard. But what exactly ST_ means? If you thought it’s “Spatial Type” you are mistaken. Below is a shorten history of SQL/MM Spatial Standardization
SQL/MM Spatial ISO/IEC 13249 SQL/MM is the effort to standardize extensions for multi-media and application-specific packages in SQL.</description></item><item><title>Admin Boundaries in BigQuery Public Datasets</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/admin-boundaries-in-bigquery-public-datasets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 06:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/admin-boundaries-in-bigquery-public-datasets/</guid><description>All US Zip Codes Geometries Visualized with Dekart When do you need Admin Boundaries in BigQuery? There are few reasons why you would need Admin Boundaries in your Data Analyses:
Your data does not have explicit coordinates or geometries but has references to Countries, States, Counties or Zip codes Admin Boundaries (like city boundary) presents a meaningful way to clip your data for analysis. You want to perform analyses per admin geography (like number of new COVID cases per state/capita) There are platforms which allow you to enrich your data with Admin Geometries, but then you lose all the power of filtering and aggregating with BigQuery SQL.</description></item><item><title>Kepler.gl + DuckDB (WASM): configuration and custom SQL UI</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/kepler.gl--duckdb-wasm-configuration-and-custom-sql-ui/</link><pubDate>Mon, 23 Feb 2026 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/kepler.gl--duckdb-wasm-configuration-and-custom-sql-ui/</guid><description>This document describes the minimal steps to:
enable DuckDB-WASM inside a Kepler.gl app, and run DuckDB SQL from a custom UI (your own editor + Run button) so the result is added to Kepler as a new dataset and auto-creates a layer. 1) Install dependencies npm install @kepler.gl/duckdb 2) Configure Kepler (required) Call initApplicationConfig once before the map is used:
import { initApplicationConfig } from &amp;#39;@kepler.gl/utils&amp;#39; import { KeplerGlDuckDbTable, DuckDBWasmAdapter } from &amp;#39;@kepler.</description></item></channel></rss>