<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog on</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 06:42:12 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dekart.xyz/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Why We Stopped using OpenStreetMap and switched to Overture Maps</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/why-we-stopped-using-openstreetmap-and-switched-to-overture-maps/</link><pubDate>Fri, 28 Jun 2024 06:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/why-we-stopped-using-openstreetmap-and-switched-to-overture-maps/</guid><description>Switching from OSM to Overture Maps Disclaimer: This article is about OpenStreetMap BigQuery Public Dataset and Overture Maps on BigQuery. Unintentionally this article raised concerns in OSM community. Clarifying edits where added to the article.
Note: Overture Maps dataset is based on OpenStreetMap data plus other sources. It is not a replacement for OpenStreetMap, but rather a more efficient way to access and work with spatial data in the cloud.</description></item><item><title>ST_ Prefix in SQL: A Tale of Time, Space, and Standardization</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/st_-prefix-in-sql-a-tale-of-time-space-and-standardization/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Mar 2024 05:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/st_-prefix-in-sql-a-tale-of-time-space-and-standardization/</guid><description>As you know, many modern databases and warehouses like BigQuery and Snowflake provide support for map geometry operations. All these functions, like ST_ASGEOJSON are prefixed with ST_. This prefix is reference to SQL/MM Spatial standard. But what exactly ST_ means? If you thought it’s “Spatial Type” you are mistaken. Below is a shorten history of SQL/MM Spatial Standardization
SQL/MM Spatial ISO/IEC 13249 SQL/MM is the effort to standardize extensions for multi-media and application-specific packages in SQL.</description></item><item><title>Admin Boundaries in BigQuery Public Datasets</title><link>https://dekart.xyz/blog/admin-boundaries-in-bigquery-public-datasets/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Mar 2021 06:59:51 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dekart.xyz/blog/admin-boundaries-in-bigquery-public-datasets/</guid><description>All US Zip Codes Geometries Visualized with Dekart When do you need Admin Boundaries in BigQuery? There are few reasons why you would need Admin Boundaries in your Data Analyses:
Your data does not have explicit coordinates or geometries but has references to Countries, States, Counties or Zip codes Admin Boundaries (like city boundary) presents a meaningful way to clip your data for analysis. You want to perform analyses per admin geography (like number of new COVID cases per state/capita) There are platforms which allow you to enrich your data with Admin Geometries, but then you lose all the power of filtering and aggregating with BigQuery SQL.</description></item></channel></rss>